<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoogleJam</string>
    <string name="Ankle_Sprain_Text"> Swipe for Images \n\n\n
        Ankle Sprain First Aid \n\n
        1.Remove ankle bracelets or toe rings right away.\n
    2.Rest the ankle. Use crutches if necessary.\n
    3.Ice the ankle for 20 to 30 minutes several times a day for the first 2 days.\n
    4.Compress by wrapping the ankle lightly,not tightly  with an Ace bandage or elastic ankle brace.\n
    5.Elevate the ankle above heart level for the first 48 hours.\n
    6.Take ibuprofen (Advil, Motrin), acetaminophen (Tylenol), or aspirin for pain. But check with your doctor first if you have any medical conditions or take any other medicines.\n
    7.Make an appointment as soon as possible for any ankle sprain, mild or severe. Do not give aspirin to anyone younger than age 19 unless told to do so by a doctor.\n
    </string>
    <string name="Dizziness">Swipe for Images \n\n\n
        Dizziness first aid \n\n
        1.The person should sit down or lie still.\n
        2.If the person gets light-headed when standing up, the person should stand up slowly.\n
        3.Avoid sudden changes in position.\n
        4.If the person is thirsty, have him or her drink fluids.\n
        5.Avoid bright lights.\n
        6.Call a health care professional if it doesn\'t go quickly.\n
    </string>
    <string name="HandFracture">Swipe for Images \n\n\n
        Hand Fracture First Aid \n\n
        1. Stop Bleeding if Necessary \n
        2. Control Swelling -Apply an ice pack (do not put ice directly against the skin).\n
        3. Immobilize the Hand -
If the person\'s hand is numb or cold or the skin under the fingernails is blue, do not move the hand or arm.\n
        4. See a health care professional immediately.\n
    </string>
    <string name="HeadInjury">Swipe for Images \n\n\n
        Head Injury First Aid \n\n
    1.To control bleeding, apply clean dressings directly to scalp or facial cuts.\n
2.To control swelling, apply ice for 20 to 30 minutes every 2 to 4 hours.\n
3.For headache, give over-the-counter acetaminophen. Do not use aspirin, ibuprofen, or other anti-inflammatory drugs, which can increase the risk of bleeding.\n
        4. See the doctor immediately.\n
    </string>
    <string name="Convulsions">Swipe for Images \n\n\n
        Convulsions First Aid \n\n
    1.Stay calm.\n
        2.Loosen anything around the person\'s neck. Do not restrain them or put anything in their mouth.\n
        3.Clear the area around them, and stay with them after the seizure stops.\n
4.Call 911 if the seizure lasts longer than 5 minutes, the person has another seizure, does not wake up, or has another medical condition.
    </string>

</resources>
